<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Search><pages Count="64"><page Index="1"/><page Index="2"/><page Index="3"><![CDATA[A





                           Codex




            f o r  G n o s t i c s







            Cosmic Comedy Writ In The Zone of Malkuth








                                              I
                         Lunacy  Trilogy  Book  I









                  Obsidian Eagle]]></page><page Index="4"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="5"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="6"><![CDATA[b
                          Also  y  Obsidian  Eagle:



                    The  Soma  Tantra:  A  Cosmic  Tragedy

                                              I
                                         B
                           (Lunacy  Trilogy  ook   )
                  Tome  of  The  Sixth  Sun:  A  Cosmic  Dramady
                                       I
                                  B
                    (Lunacy  Trilogy  ook  II;  ongoing  online)




                              Forthcoming:



                  Future  Sutras:  A  Decade  of  Anti-Poetry]]></page><page Index="7"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="8"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="9"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="10"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="11"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="12"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="13"><![CDATA[≋




                                    &


                 For Shannon





                                     ≋]]></page><page Index="14"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="15"><![CDATA[T A B L E    O F  C O N T E N T S




            Map of the Megalocosmos . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . ix
                                    .
            Prologu                  .
                   e: Brax’s Brouhaha . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . 1
                               .
            Act One    : Overtures . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . 13

            Act  Two:  Incarnations . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . 27
                                 .
                                       .
            Act  Three: Transfigurations . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . 45

            Act  Four: Pan-Gaeah . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . 75
                                .

            Act  Five: Zyberyuh . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . 101
                              .

                                   .
            Epil  ogue: Æon of Zaynh . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . 139

                                             .
            Glossary    of Recondite Terminology . . . . . . . . . . 153

            Appendix:
                        Decoded For Dummies. . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . 165

            * Page numbers correspond to 1st edition.





            Blank pages, illustrations, and informal plates are

            discounted.]]></page><page Index="16"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="17"><![CDATA[“Hell is empty
                          And all the devils are here.”

                     ~ from The Tempest by William Shakespeare



                                    ≈


                    “Maybe this world is another planet’s Hell.”

                               ~ Aldous Huxley


                                    ≈



                     “Every Man and every Woman is a Star.”


                               ~ Aleister Crowley

                                    ≈


                                “Here are we

                            One magical movement

                           from Kether to Malkuth.”
                      ~ from Station To Station by David Bowie]]></page><page Index="18"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="19"><![CDATA[WARNING





             This book contains many hard to read names

             (modified from Egyptian and Persian sources)

             which are probably too difficult for the average

             English speaker to pronounce. This was done

             deliberately because A) It conveys that beings in

             other parts of the universe probably speak in a

             manner that is completely alien to us and

             B) A cypher differentiates the divinities

             mentioned here from those whose

             names might be devalued by their

             misuse in mainstream media.

             For readers having trouble, a new Appendix:

             Decoded For Dummies has been provided.

             However it is suggested that the reader gleans over

             such names without too much fuss. Otherwise,

             abandon all hope, ye who enter here!]]></page><page Index="20"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="21"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="22"><![CDATA[Dramatis Personæ





             Cast of Characters (in order of appearance)

            Prologue Section


            Baal Abraxah — AKA Brax — The Alpha
            Arkhonh. Lord of Lucifer’s Aster.


            Race: Arkhonh (singular) / Arkhonz
            (plural). These Arkhonz are a demoniac
            species; the apex predators at the top of the
            food chain in a conflictual cosmos. Brax
            himself is the cause of a holy commotion.

            Together with six other Arkhonz, he
            commits high treason against Amoun-Rah
            in the highest zone of Ketheroz.]]></page><page Index="23"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="24"><![CDATA[Amoun-Rah, Preceptor of Neterz and Lord

            over Ketheroz.

            Amoun-Rah acts as a stand-in for ‘God’
            throughout the Megalocosmos.



            Race: Neterh (singular) / Neterz (plural).
            The most evolved beings in existence, these
            Neterz preside over the Interstellar
            Panopticon. Their godlike powers allow
            them to remain isolated from the lower
            zones for many Æons, at least until Baal
            Abraxah rouses his rebellion against them.]]></page><page Index="25"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="26"><![CDATA[Amoun-Rah is often surrounded by a sextet

            of Archangels called the Amezhah
            Zpentaz. These six are known as:


            Armaythyh, Ameretath, and Haurvatath —
            the female triplets.


            Race: Archangels; Zpentah (singular) /
            Zpentaz (plural).


            This sorority is complemented by three
            distinct brothers…]]></page><page Index="27"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="28"><![CDATA[Kzhathrah Vayryuh, ‘righteous power’.


            Race: Zpentah / Zpentaz.


            Wielding a massive war hammer, this
            Archangel is a force to be reckoned with.]]></page><page Index="29"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="30"><![CDATA[Vohuh-Manah, ‘splendid mind’.


            Race: Zpentah / Zpentaz.


            Vohuh-Manah’s chrono-staff can
            manipulate short periods of time.]]></page><page Index="31"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="32"><![CDATA[Azhah Vahyzthah, ‘excellent order’ AKA

            The Omega Amezhah Zpentah.

            Race: Zpentah / Zpentaz.


            Azhah’s element is primal fire, thus he
            wields a flaming sword. Azhah is fearless
            leader of the Amezhah Zpentaz.



            These six Archangels comprise Amoun-
            Rah’s honor guard and are his staunch
            enforcers. They also lead large armies
            composed of two other angelic orders;
            Fravahz & Yazadz.]]></page><page Index="33"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="34"><![CDATA[Hazzanh, Scion of Toolooph, King of

            Karataz.


            Race: Arkhonh / Arkhonz.


            Hazzanh is Baal Abraxah’s grandson, whom
            ascends to the throne during Brax’s exile.]]></page><page Index="35"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="36"><![CDATA[Overture Section



            Theuth, Scribe of Neterz.

            Race: Neterh / Neterz.


            Theuth dons the Crest of Ibis as his
            ceremonial headdress. He obviously
            represents the author’s own inspiration.]]></page><page Index="37"><![CDATA[Theuth]]></page><page Index="38"><![CDATA[Vortexyuh, Daughter of Nuyth.


            Race: Neterh / Neterz.


            Vortexyuh is the youngest of the Neterz but
            also charged as The Heavenly Gatekeeper
            and (with notable exceptions) she controls
            traffic along every pathway of the
            Zephyroth, throughout the whole wide

            Megalocosmos.]]></page><page Index="39"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="40"><![CDATA[Maath, Mater of Matter, Creatrix Supreme.


            Race: Neterh / Neterz.


            A matriarchal Neterh whom oversees the
            material plane on Amoun-Rah’s behalf.
            Geometry Gnomes responsible for putting
            into action the fundamental laws of physics
            are directed by Mistress Maath (shown here

            backed by Ammuth and holding the scales
            of justice).]]></page><page Index="41"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="42"><![CDATA[Horuz AKA Rah-Hoor-Khuth; The Hawk

            Headed Lord.

            Race: Neterh / Neterz.


            An infuriated and warlike Neterh, Horuz’
            motivation is vengeance against those of us
            who dwell on planet Tellz (Earth), mid the
            solar system of Orz, in the material zone of

            Malkuth.

            There are many more players in this saga,
            however, those introduced herewith are the

            most important at least until the story starts
            to unfold.]]></page><page Index="43"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="44"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="45"><![CDATA[Map of The Megalocosmos]]></page><page Index="46"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="47"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="48"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="49"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="50"><![CDATA[O b s i d i a n  E a g l e

          because soon thereafter those seven Arkhonz established their
          new law across creation: Heptaparah-Parzhynokh. By virtue of
          said law, they were able to envelop themselves within the self-
          same fabric of reality. Thus it became possible for mortals to
          call upon them if they understood how to properly use The
          Octave. Even now as you read this, that Octave holds true.
          Anyway, let us return to our story.

             Having instilled the Law of Seven, the Arkhonz proceeded
          to raise several large armies in the middling zone of Geburah.
          In fact, their ranks swelled so much that they even spilled over
          into the neighbouring zone of Zhezedh. These forces were com-
          prised from a variety of higher-vibration entities than those
          found on any organic sphere. Namely: Arkturyunz, ancient
          Blengynz and Glandelynz, Norz of Pleydyuh, and Zetaz from
          both Retykulyh. Their ultimate goal of course, was deposing
          Amoun off the throne of Ketheroz in order to install Brax
          there instead. However, since there is no direct route between
          either Geburah or Zhezedh toward the Sun Absolute at the
          galactic centre—a dual assault had to be mounted against the
          twin cities in the secondary zones of Bynah and Zhokmah. It
          was there that the most epic struggle in all the Megalocosmos
          came to a head.

             Houses Bynah and Zhokmah are residences to obscenely
          powerful Archangels, which only rally to Ketheroz’ call when-
          ever it becomes necessary for them to Etherealize within a given
          galaxy. They have extensive experience battling throughout the
          myriad worlds of many star systems. So it was that when the
          trans-dimensional longships of the Arkhonh alliance approached
          the gold and silver towers via vortexes Vauh and Zheth these
          were immediately met by hosts of winged Fravahz and Yazadz,



                                   2]]></page><page Index="51"><![CDATA[A  C o d e x  F o r  G n o s t i c s

              under the expert command of undefeated luminaries best known
              as Amezhah Zpentaz.
                Hundreds of ships were destroyed during the first few
              moments after arrival. Nevertheless, this turned out to be
              no straightforward battle. Brax and his allies employed the
              Sevenfold Law to its utmost degree; manipulating time itself
              allowed their legions to take out scores of celestial guardians.
              It was a ferocious conflict that carried nigh unto the front steps
              of Bynah and Zhokmah alike. The astral and planetary damage
              wrought by supernal armaments brandished then was enough
              to leave starry artifacts such as nebulae and quasars for us to
              behold even at present.

                Brax’s soldiers from the extrinsic zones clustered into tight
              phalanxes as they debarked their vessels. Firing beams of accel-
              erated particles to down the angelical paladins of those intrin-
              sic zones, they gained lots of ground versus either Fravahz or
              Yazadz, before the Amezha Zpentaz decided to intervene. Solar
              beings born of a superior zone, even the Sevenfold Law could
              not serve to impede those six glorious Archangels. The three
              females (Ameretath, Armaythyh, and Haurvatath) subdued
              struggling swarms of Arkturyunz, Blengynz, Glandelynz, Norz,
              and Zetaz. Kzhathrah Vayryuh, whose name means ‘righ-
              teous power’ flexed his mettle against the Arkhonz: Molokh,
              Zhamazh, and Yarykh. Vohuh-Manah, whose name means
              ‘splendid mind’ occupied himself with Arkhonz: Angrah,
              Azhtaroth, and Beryth. Leaving their leader Azhah Vahyzthah
              whose name means ‘excellent order’ to deal with Brax.

                Altercations continued at a fever pitch as the two gener-
              als squared off somewhere amidst the affray. Azhah and Brax
              were within Bynah and Zhokmah simultaneously since they



                                      3]]></page><page Index="52"><![CDATA[O b s i d i a n  E a g l e

          possessed the ability to split their Khabz and Khuh. But sud-
          denly those scenes at the foot of each citadel vanished. Then
          Abraxah and Azhah were alone within a void. Resplendent as
          the Zohar itself, Azhah Vahyzthah drew his flaming sword and
          raised an adamantine shield engraved with a balance before he
          spoke thus wise:

             “Baal Abraxah—Alpha Arkhonh and Lord of Lucifer’s
          Aster—I have crossed the paths named Daleth and Gymelh to
          collapse our Khabz and Khuh back together and bring us down
          into the shadow zone of Daath. Here by order of Amoun-Rah,
          Preceptor of Neterz, voice of Ayn, shalt thou be disposed by
          myself, his mightiest pupil!”

             For his part, Brax let drop a spiky sphere of antimatter
          attached to a hex chain.
             He also unfurled a whip made of superstring fiber with his
          left hand. Each contender spread out six wings (Azhah’s bright
          gossamer; Abraxah’s black feathered) like peacocks about to
          joust. Then came Brax’s retort:

             “Azhah Vahyzthah—Omega Amezhah Zpentah and
          Champion of Ahurah Mazdah—hast thou forsworn thy true
          master that ye profess to fight on behalf of Amoun-Rah?”

             “Lo Baal Abraxah! Ketheroz is home to the most high in
          all universes including this one. In some my master is Ahurah,
          while in others ’tis Amoun. At another time thou wert known
          to me as Ahrymanh, King of Daevaz. Each Macrocosm differs
          slightly just as a tale changes depending on its teller. Art thou
          mortal to abide by any appellative quite so fixedly?”

             Brax’s shoulders shrugged with laughter, but he said nothing.
          Springing into action he went after Azhah, wielding morning


                                   4]]></page><page Index="53"><![CDATA[A  C o d e x  F o r  G n o s t i c s

              star and whip in tandem. When the spikes crashed against
              Azhah’s shield, the antimatter ball imploded and offset the
              Archangel enough for Brax to lasso half his wings. Nonetheless,
              Excellent Order didn’t miss a step — he cut through that
              binding tether with his blazing blade. Defence turned to offence
              when Azhah pushed back using the balance buckler. Brax
              managed   to   save   himself   from   a   sword   strike   only   by
              invoking Heptaparah-Parzhynokh. Even then fanning flames
              did scathe him. Now Azhah Vahyzthah openly teased Brax:
                “It is of no use to rely on your paltry law, for its effects
              are limited within Daath. Surrender or else suffer a summary
              sentence!”

                “I wouldst never capitulate to that smug tyranny of Ketheroz!
              Prepare yourself Archangel. I have saved the best for last. Behold,
              the beast called Levyuhthanh comes.”

                Surely enough, something massive appeared to rend through
              the veil of the void:

                A dragon of unfathomable proportions, whose body was
              made from all the elements of the material plane. Brax flapped
              his wings and flew onto the head of this colossus. Swinging
              his hex chain made the morning star reignite. Thus he charged
              toward the Amezhah Zpentah once more as Levyuhthanh
              spewed entropy upon its beastly breath.

                It was only a matter of time before Azhah’s perfect barrier
              was worn away beneath that exhalation’s sheer magnitude.
              Unperturbed when his shield rapidly disintegrated, he under-
              took evasive manoeuvres, though dodging was not his main aim.
              Instead, as he zigzagged from point A to Z (and everywhere
              in between) he left behind a fiery trail singed by his weapon.



                                      5]]></page><page Index="54"><![CDATA[O b s i d i a n  E a g l e

             Having traversed the seemingly immeasurable length of
          Levyuhthanh, Azhah Vahyzthah raised his rapier, stabbing into
          a gaseous cyclone overhead. The seething pentagram, which had
          just been drawn, started tightening from end to end and con-
          stricting Levyuhthanh’s movements. While the drake struggled
          angrily against that snare, its entire breadth began going up in
          blazes very fast. Yet it spat out another abysmal expectoration
          before being burnt to ashes. This projectile was painstakingly
          deflected by Azhah, leaving him momentarily open to an attack.
             Brax abandoned his pet beast, lunging at Azhah in a last-
          ditch attempt to overwhelm the opponent. Those efforts were
          not in vain because Azhah was still recovering. The antimatter
          flail found its mark square in the Archangel’s armour, breaking
          his breastplate and knocking him backward. Rainbow tinted
          filaments emanated from the inflicted wound!
             “It hath been remarkably long since last I beheld mine own
          blessed blood. Such a slight cannot go unanswered. Thy Will
          be broken Baal Abraxah!”

             Azhah Vahyztha’s falchion flared anew and its brilliancy
          blinded Brax for an instant. The Omega Amezhah Zpentah
          seized this important opportunity to slip that sabre’s pointy tip
          through the Alpha Arkhonz’ chain mail, piercing his dark heart!

             The two immortal enemies stood there a little longer than
          Brax needed to say:

             “Be thee cursed, Azhah Vahyzthah! What I hast initiated
          shalt yet reach its apex. Another wilt arise to avenge me.”

             Thence with those words, his metaphysical aggregates dis-
          sipated from Daath.




                                   6]]></page><page Index="55"><![CDATA[A  C o d e x  F o r  G n o s t i c s

                But of course, he wasn’t actually dead. What he knew next
              was opening his eyes to see the court of Ketheroz, with all its
              arbiters assembled there as witnesses to his trial. Shackles bound
              his wrists and ankles. That amphitheatre chattered loudly until
              an entity more sublime than any other imaginable had begun to
              Etherealize on the lucent throne. Upon his crown were swirling
              the skies of many worlds. His face was like the visage of every
              noble monument ever erected. Oceanic luster spilled wherever
              his vision rested. The six Amezhah Zpentaz wreathed him like
              candles, comprising an honour guard. Yea! Amoun-Rah’s tone
              shook the cornerstones of that divine edifice:
                “Baal Abraxah, Alpha Arkhonh and Lord of Lucifer’s Aster.
              Thou art charged with treason beyond discernible reason.
              Indeed, thy sins be so severe that neither jury nor prosecutors
              are needed to ascertain thy guilt. What transpired is clear to
              everyone here. Hence shalt thee be stripped of supernatural
              powers and exiled to the lowest zone of Malkuth until thy star
              exhausts its natural elements. Perhaps then thou canst compre-
              hend the utility of humility. Know that when Lucifer expires,
              thou too wilt pass into the Infinite Interval. Hath thou any-
              thing to add or ask?”

                Brax paused pensively for a few seconds before adding
              and asking:
                “Although aware that this congregation owes me little leni-
              ency, I offer no apologies. Ayn Zoph Aur makes us all what we
              are. Yet do I plead for the privilege of visiting mine home in the
              zone of Typhareth a final time prior to undergoing Abstruction.”
                There was a general clamour disapproving of Brax’s entreaty
              but it went quiet when the Amezhah Zpentaz sounded a fanfare.
              Affably, Amoun answered:


                                      7]]></page><page Index="56"><![CDATA[O b s i d i a n  E a g l e

             “Very well. Let it not be said that Ketheroz is incapable of
          clemency. Thy wish wilt be granted, although not until this
          sentence is served. When that term endeth, minimal assistance
          shalt be lent thee to arrange one last journey back to Typhareth.”

             At the dismissive wave of Amoun-Rah’s right hand, Brax
          was promptly banished to a backwater solar system the high
          ones called Orz. Within Orz, Brax took up residence on a red
          planet which he dubbed Marz. There he built himself an obser-
          vatory and soon became aware of a primitive species of sentient
          beings who dwelt on the third planet outward from that system’s
          saffron sun. Brax also discovered that the other six Arkhonz
          were imprisoned on various nearby spheres. It didn’t take him
          long to devise ways of communicating with them to coordi-
          nate furtive forays on the third orb, which they named Tellz.
             These divested demiurges developed a vested interest in
          Tellz’ dawning primates. Abraxah and his allies spurred their
          development, imparting bountiful esoteric knowledge over
          immemorial millennia spanning the supercontinent of Pan-
          Gaeah. Although it did come at a cost; protean man’s subtle
          cytology was altered irrevocably. For example, whereas those
          creatures were originally sexless, therewith they divided in two
          separate genders. Furthermore, the Arkhonz started to worry
          about their untapped potential to Etherealize. For this reason,
          they implanted an undetectable organ below the coccyx of the
          first female members of a new species, ensuring that it would
          be passed on indefinitely to all their heirs. That organ is known
          as the infamous Kundahbuffer.

             These advanced mammals were henceforth referred to as
          Homz by the Arkhonz, whose whole gamut was rendered insen-
          sible via Kundahbuffer’s suppressive agency. Thus they could



                                   8]]></page><page Index="57"><![CDATA[A  C o d e x  F o r  G n o s t i c s

              continue controlling the collective destiny of Homz, having
              anchored base consciousnesses to Tellz utilizing naught but
              temporal   concerns.   Concurrently,   Abraxah,   Angrah,
              Azhtaroth, Beryth, Molokh, Yarykh, and Zhamazh each
              enjoyed worship from groups of Homz that they pitted like
              pawns in a game against one another. Emboldened by those
              exploits, they reinstated a limited albeit pivotal version of their
              Heptaparah-Parzhynokh. In this way Brax subverted Orz
              beneath his mandate.
                Yet withal, he knew that his time was running out.
                When the fated day finally arrived, a trans-dimensional
              longship entered orbit around Marz and a delegation descended
              to speak with Baal Abraxah. Chief among them were the pilot
              Ahoonh, and a young captain Hazzanh (whom it so happened
              was Brax’s own grandson). However, Brax didn’t become con-
              scious of this fact until after the princeling introduced himself:

                “Greetings from Typhareth, Baal Abraxah! I am Hazzanh—
              scion of thy son Toolooph and king of our home world Karataz.
              A messenger from Ketheroz recently revealed your whereabouts
              to us and free passage hast been granted us by Vortexyuh; hence
              have we come aboard the spaceship Karnakh to ferry you unto
              Lucifer’s Aster.”

                Brax’s face lit up when he recognized his proximate progeny,
              but its colour faded a bit as he murmured:

                “If thou art king, kindly lad, then that means thy father
              Toolooph—”
                Hazzanh nodded solemnly and related:

                “Father would not willingly relinquish control of Typhareth
              in the aftermath of thine attack on the twin towers. He waged



                                      9]]></page><page Index="58"><![CDATA[O b s i d i a n  E a g l e

          a bitter battle in high orbit above Karataz and was dealt an
          instantaneous Abstruction in the field. I was but a boy on the
          surface then, so Ketheroz staid its blades. It was condoned
          that I be coronated; since my sovereignty is symbolic at best.”

             “Why, that is most egregious my dear boy!” Grandsire Brax
          grumbled gruffly. Placing a hand on his grandson’s shoulder
          he urged:
             “We shan’t delay, for Lucifer shalt soon see its last day. Let
          us board the Karnakh and discuss these matters on the way.”

             Which is what they did. Brax began bequeathing his arcane
          wisdom to Hazzanh as well because they had light years
          ahead of them and the crowned prince hadn’t ever received
          such instruction on the use of his budding abilities. He was
          a swift learner though, making grandfather Brax quite proud.
          Being kindred, the king was excited to hear marvellous tales
          about planet Tellz and its lowly worms (the foolhardy Homz).
          Eventually they reached their natal zone of Typhareth after
          passing through quasi-space in Tauh, stellar clusters amid zone
          Yezodh, and the interstice where pathway Peh intersects with
          that of Zamekh. By then Hazzanh had become adept at ignit-
          ing his astral essence. Following an expeditious reentry, Brax
          attended a brief conference on Karataz and got familial affairs
          in order.

             Once again they departed, heading for the heart of that
          system—Lucifer’s Aster.
             Its radiance as they approached was awe-inspiring to say the
          least. Along with Ahoonh, Baal Abraxah and Hazzanh watched
          the star’s dying spasms as it swelled to extremities. Lucifer’s
          effulgence outshone not only the galactic core, but adjacent



                                  10]]></page><page Index="59"><![CDATA[A  C o d e x  F o r  G n o s t i c s

              galaxies too. Vibrating intensely for an indefinite period, it
              exploded violently and would have destroyed the Karnakh,
              were Ahoonh not an adroit ace! Meanwhile Baal Abraxah dis-
              appeared next to Hazzanh on the observation deck.

                Time and space were now distorted in a blurry, chaotic
              disaster. A black cavity drew every free-floating glimmer hur-
              riedly into juggernaut jaws killing Lucifer.
                Zaps yielded X-rays—whirlpool vacuum unleashed ter-
              rific squalls!

                And yet the Karnakh coasted atop the crests of many oncom-
              ing waves.
                As Hazzanh looked on that breathtaking sight, he noticed
              that Brax’s amplified form was beginning to coalesce amid the
              epicentre of the maelstrom. The king’s seventh sense perked up,
              and he was able to hear his grandsire deliver a final message:

                Take heed Scion of Toolooph, even a prince plays the putz when
              cast in foreign lands. If thou wouldst become a Magus Magnus useth
              this blackened brightness to build a base. Here canst thee channel
              sufficient raw energy to rouse a new Neterh capable of contesting
              Ketheroz. Reforge our alliances with Geburah and Zhezedh. Also
              reopen Typhareth’s borders to zones Hodh and Netzakh. Last but not
              least, oversee life on Tellz and make sure that its Homz remain bliss-
              fully ignorant of their place in the greater scheme of things. Amoun-
              Rah himself doesn’t realize how important a foothold Orz is.
                Having transmitted those details, Brax was Abstructed into
              the Infinite Interval. That gaping chasm below became calmer,
              and the Karnakh turned about to Karataz. King Hazzanh
              obeyed Brax, returning to raise a fortress he christened Ormenh
              over the foundation provided by that supermassive fissure in


                                      11]]></page><page Index="60"><![CDATA[O b s i d i a n  E a g l e

          Yetzyrah’s mesh. Its dynamic erection flaunted grandiose hand-
          iwork. Nothing like it existed elsewhere. Avoiding disorder,
          Hazzanh cleared the adjoining gateways Lamedh, Yodh, Aynh,
          and Nunh. Further, he used zones Hodh and Netzakh as staging
          points for dispatching agents to Malkuth via Zhynh and Quoph,
          but he also sent others down through Rezh and Tzaddyh to settle
          a lunar outpost in zone Yezodh. He kept a close eye on Tellz
          this entire time. Bringing us into the present moment.














































                                  12]]></page><page Index="61"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="62"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="63"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="64"/></pages></Search>
